I made a list of all the World cup matches we'll watch on your new widescreen TV.
Our first game is at Bloemfontein, then in Durban, then we go to Cape Town for the semi-final.
If everything goes well and we don't mess up
...we will face Brazil in the the final at Soccer City, in Johannesburg.
That will be such a wonderful game.  I love those Brazilian drums and all the singing.
My Fuhrer...
FIFA...
FIFA thought about it, but decided not to ban the vuvuzela.
So there won't be singing, drums, or cowbells.
Stay.  If you have a vuvuzela.
Kitel
Yodel
Kripps
and Buto.
I'm going to shove them up your ass!
Those damn horns are ruining the World Cup.
I just spent five grand on a TV and a surround sound system.
Oh God, the wife will kill me.
It sounds like a swarm of bees in my house.
Buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz.  That's all I can ever hear!
For 90 minutes.  The entire bloody match!
I might as well stuff tampons in my ears
My Fuhrer, you could mute the TV?
Then how the hell will I know what is going on?
Fuhrer, the vuvuzela is a cultural icon in South Africa
Cultural icon my ass.  It's a plastic bloody trumpet!
The World Cup is for EVERYONE!
That damn horn was only made in 2001
by a plastics company in Cape Town.
Where is the insult in banning it at World Cup matches?
There are over 300 million people just like me...
watching in their slippers at home
suffering through 90 minutes of tuneless droning trumpets.
It gives me a bloody fucking headache.
I just want to enjoy the game.  Is that too much to ask?
Our boys on the pitch can't hear themselves think
...or their supporters chanting and singing!
You all know me.  I'm a reasonable man.
But this is the beautiful game...
It's for the World.  Only every few years.
Sepp fucking Blatter.
That so called President of FIFA.
Him and the rest of FIFA totally fucked it up.
I swear I'll just give up following the German Team completely.
And I'm stuck with useless five thousand dollar home theater.
Do you know what 30,000 vuvuzelas sounds like...
when you have a 17 speaker surround sound system?
Don't worry.  You can use ear plugs.
I may give up football. Take up golf.
It's just unbearable. I can't watch it anymore.
Mr. Strauss
and Kripps.
I've had it.
Go upstairs.  Find the packing case for the TV and the surround sound system.
Pack it all up. And don't forget the remote control.
I'll call the Sony dealer and they can come collect it tomorrow.
Such a shame.